[
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "95A_Sadiki_Topic01",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@95A_S02_GlimpseofthePast_TalkSage_Prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@95A_S02_GlimpseofthePast_TalkSage",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "ProvidedTopics": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "95A_Sharif_Topic01",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@95A_S02_WordofaThief_MeetSharif_Prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@95A_S02_WordofaThief_MeetSharif",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "ProvidedTopics": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "95A_Sharif_Topic01a",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@95A_S02_WordofaThief_FreeSharif_Prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@95A_S02_WordofaThief_FreeSharif",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "ProvidedTopics": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "95A_Sharif_Topic02",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@95A_S02_HardBoiled_TalkSharif_Prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@95A_S02_HardBoiled_TalkSharif",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "ProvidedTopics": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "95A_Sharif_Topic03",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@95A_S02_SecondThoughts_TalkSharif_Prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@95A_S02_SecondThoughts_TalkSharif",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "ProvidedTopics": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "95A_Sharif_Topic04",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@95A_S02_SecondThoughts_HideSharif_Prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@95A_S02_SecondThoughts_HideSharif",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "ProvidedTopics": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "95A_Sharif_Topic05",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@95A_S02_SecondThoughts_AmbushSharif_Prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@95A_S02_SecondThoughts_AmbushSharif",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "ProvidedTopics": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "95A_Sharif_Topic06",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@95A_S02_HeiroftheSands_TalkSharif_Prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@95A_S02_HeiroftheSands_TalkSharif",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "ProvidedTopics": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "95A_Sharif_Topic07",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@95A_S02_HeiroftheSands_MeetSharif_Prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@95A_S02_HeiroftheSands_MeetSharif",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "ProvidedTopics": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "95A_Sharif_Topic08",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@95A_S02_EmptyNest_TalkSharif_Prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@95A_S02_EmptyNest_TalkSharif",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "ProvidedTopics": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "95A_Sharif_Topic09",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@95A_S02_BreakSomeEggs_TalkSharif_Prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@95A_S02_BreakSomeEggs_TalkSharif",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "ProvidedTopics": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "95A_Sharif_Topic10",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@95A_S02_LegacyoftheSands_TalkSharif_Prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@95A_S02_LegacyoftheSands_TalkSharif",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "ProvidedTopics": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "95A_Sharif_Topic11",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@95A_S02_Remembrance_TalkSharif_Prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@95A_S02_Remembrance_TalkSharif",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "ProvidedTopics": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "95A_Rima_Topic01",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@95A_S02_VoicesoftheDesert_TalkRima_Prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@95A_S02_VoicesoftheDesert_TalkRima",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "ProvidedTopics": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "95A_Rima_Topic02",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@95A_S02_VoicesoftheDesert_RimaSong_Prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@95A_S02_VoicesoftheDesert_RimaSong",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "ProvidedTopics": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "95A_Rima_Topic03",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@95A_S02_VoicesoftheDesert_RimaJoin_Prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@95A_S02_VoicesoftheDesert_RimaJoin",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "ProvidedTopics": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "95A_Rima_Topic04",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@95A_S02_SecondThoughts_TalkRima_Prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@95A_S02_SecondThoughts_TalkRima",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "ProvidedTopics": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "95A_Rima_Topic05",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@95A_S02_EggHunt_TalkRima_Prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@95A_S02_EggHunt_TalkRima",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "ProvidedTopics": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "95A_Rima_Topic06",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@95A_S02_Remembrance_TalkRima_Prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@95A_S02_Remembrance_TalkRima",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "ProvidedTopics": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "95A_Zander_Topic01",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@95A_S02_VoicesoftheDesert_TalkZander_Prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@95A_S02_VoicesoftheDesert_TalkZander",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "ProvidedTopics": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "95A_Zander_Topic02",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@95A_S02_EggHunt_TalkZander_Prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@95A_S02_EggHunt_TalkZander",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "ProvidedTopics": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "95A_Zander_Topic03",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@95A_S02_EggHunt_MeetZander_Prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@95A_S02_EggHunt_MeetZander",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "ProvidedTopics": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "95A_Zander_Topic04",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@95A_S02_PrecariousPosition_ZanderRuins_Prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@95A_S02_PrecariousPosition_ZanderRuins",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "ProvidedTopics": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "95A_Zander_Topic05",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@95A_S02_HeiroftheSands_TalkZander_Prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@95A_S02_HeiroftheSands_TalkZander",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "ProvidedTopics": ""
    },
    {
        "ConversationTopicId": "95A_Jackal_Topic01",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@95A_S02_VoicesoftheDesert_TalkJackal_Prompt",
        "NPCResponse": "@95A_S02_VoicesoftheDesert_TalkJackal",
        "AchievementUnlock": "",
        "RequiredAchievement": "",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "ProvidedTopics": ""
    }
]
